It's been dull without
so many orders lately.
We've been too busy up to now.
It's like it's been Black Friday.
We've been working too hard.
If we took our case to
an animal rights group—
or whatever the right outfit is, we might
be able to get fair compensation.
Wow, you're really starting
to sound like a human, huh?
We need to assert our rights, too!
These days, cats are creatures
that deserve respect,
not the property of human beings.
That's the trend out there.
Cats are cats. I think you're
overstating the case.
However, I do agree with you that
cats are deserving of some dignity.
Yeah, I wish they would
take a page from us,
but unlike us furry beasts,
those hairless, naked
animals are heartless.
It may not do us any
good to count on them.
Guys, supper's ready.
Sitting under the kotatsu like this,
I'm kind of getting
a craving for ice cream.
No! Grandma, you meanie!
I want ice cream!
You can't have any.
Wah! I hate you!
Ordinarily, right now,
there'd be some boring news on the TV,
and Mom would be putting
her gross cooking on the table.
Her mom hated us
something terrible, didn't she?
She was someone who
couldn't even tell the difference
between cat hair and ordinary dust.
I wish I could go back home.
There she goes, wishing
for the impossible again.
For heaven's sake,
she doesn't understand a thing.
Do you think so?
Mizuho is 16 years old now.
If she were a cat, it would be crazy
if she hadn't had any kittens yet.
Well, aren't you a modern cat?
Those animal groups would
have something to say about that.
Oh, buzz off.
Mizuho is still a child.
She couldn't survive without us around.
Okay, let's have some ice cream.
I'll give you this.
No! Not until you get back.
What did she want us to bring this time?
Ice cream.
By when?
She said right away.
Is there time?
Hmm... we'll try our best.
You there! Are you here as warriors?!
No, we're...
Then why are you here?!
We're... You see, we just want...
We want you to make up with Seiji.
Your little quarrel is
bothering everyone else.
In this world,
there is only the duel
between me and my brother!
Whew, we made it in time.
If you don't want to get
caught in the middle of it,
then leave this world!
Whoa, scary.
Okay, what do we do?
I told you this is what would happen.
Your twin brother is quite, um...
...grouchy, isn't he?
Yeah.
Unlike me, he's really narrow minded.
Well, is it true that the cause of your
fighting is a single strand of hair?
Yes, it is!
I have 110,635 hairs,
while Sou has 110,634!
I have one more hair than he does.
We've counted a million times,
so there's no mistake.
Talk about wigging out over nothing.
Heh, I think so, too.
If he would just be honest about me
beating him, this would all be over.
Still, Nagara and Mizuho,
thanks for coming.
I was right to talk to Nozomi about this.
We'll do whatever we can.
Mm-hmm.
We got caught up in this
and didn't know what to do.
Ms. Aki has gone off
somewhere else, and...
Huh?
What's that look for?
Nothing. I was just wondering how
long you were going to keep that up.
Oh, cram it.
How mature is that?
Damn it!
Gah! Repulsive bunch.
Every last one of you.
Poor fellow.
He goes off in a huff
and sulks when he feels snubbed.
I'll wager he got shot down by Nozomi.
He can't win her heart.
Harsh, but accurate.
If we're going to change the world,
we need the power those twins have.
But...
...we only need one of them.
Dosukoi!
Wrong! Watch me do it!
Private Kaga, you try it!
Dosukoi!
Why, you! This is a
damn fine piece of meat!
Where did you get it?!
I-It was given to me by Seiji!
Gottsuan!
Don't you "gottsuan" me, you moron!
I thought I told you not
to get too close to him!
Gottsuan—
Why...
...can't you keep your promises?!
Why?!
Those two twins really are fighting each
other over a single strand of hair, huh?
Mm-hmm, that's what he said.
Wait, you're not thinking...
Yeah. That's what I'm thinking.
We pluck a hair off the one who has more,
and show it to both of them.
Do you think it will really be that easy?
Mm-hmm.
Can you think of a better way?
Hmm... How about a hair transplant?
It seemed like there was a power
holdover for this sort of thing...
W-Was that...?
Mm-hmm, "Reverse."
How should we compete this time around?
"Reverse," the power the twins possess,
is able to rewind everything,
and reset the world.
It was suggested that if that happened,
then those of us in stasis
could possibly return to
just before we went adrift.
It was suggested?
This is the bottom of a giant crater.
This place could have been reset
any number of times already.
But, since it's a reset,
the twins don't seem to remember it.
I guess they wouldn't, huh?
Moreover, since both
twins can use "Reverse,"
even if one of them uses "Reverse,"
if the other one uses "Reverse" too,
then that rewinding gets
rewound back to the way it was.
And that's how these two twins' conflict
has gone on for thousands of years.
They call it a "Reverse-Reverse."
Yeah, but it's not just Sou and Seiji
working their powers.
There's also the duel that's always being
carried on when their power activates.
Duel?
Mm-hmm.
Wow, that's amazing.
So there are cheat-code powers
that let you do resets, huh?
Hmm?
What's this?
"Sou Seiji"...
Huh? You mean those two
aren't twins after all?
Does this mean...?
Don't you feel pathetic?
You keep losing to yourself.
That guy isn't me! I'm me!
Would you like some help?
No!
You may have started out being the same,
but you're different now.
I'll beat him on my own.
You're a believer, too, aren't you?
This is God's divine protection.
They look like they're the same,
but they aren't perfectly similar.
There are slight variations in each copy.
Keep it to yourself, dog.
I heard that.
Have you been listening in the whole time?
Yeah, starting at some point.
It speaks pretty poorly of your
character not to say anything until now.
Yeah, I could never find the
right moment to mention it.
Nyamazon stuff is essentially
a bunch of copies, right?
Why ask me?
Why?
Because you're the
one doing the copying, right?
You know what? I can appreciate you.
You're unusually negative for a dog.
But more than anything,
you're good to Mizuho.
The reason we kept it to
ourselves is for Mizuho's sake.
If this got out, she's the one
the blame would fall on.
Then again, if this had gotten out,
they would have been able to go home
for certain when they had the chance.
Back to the future they wanted.
Are you sure you kept it
to yourselves for her sake?
What are you insinuating?
That you're actually doing it
for yourselves, aren't you?
You're afraid that if you leave Mizuho—
You're wrong.
That girl
can't get by without me.
I don't think that's true.
The first one who noticed was that boy
who is unusually smart for a child.
...fifty USB cables,
and a box of Sudakosan Taro.
A crowd-funded game I once
wrote for the PocketGame.
You wrote? Badass.
Mm-hmm. What's more,
only one was ever sold.
It became known as a legendary
one-of-a-kind game among the fans.
Oh, yeah? You Indians are something else.
So what kind of game is it?
It's a highly-insidious,
impossibly-hard game.
The goal is to encounter
a single predetermined tick
out of trillions of possible classmates,
and have it declare its love for you.
It's a romantic simulation game.
Whoa, that sounds super-fun!
I worked extra-hard on
working out the ticks' emotions.
Anyhow, I need it to refer to for
this next world we're conquering.
Is that okay?
Sure.
Oh, but these are off-limits.
I've made a few orders of my own,
but those cats won't bring
me anything that's alive.
Aw, I was afraid of that.
Thank you for your business.
The only one of its kind in
the world, and now there's...
...two of them...
We have been copied.
He knew that he did not fully
understand both his and Mizuho's powers.
So, what do you think I should do?
What is my power, anyway?
It was then that he chose a
different subject to investigate.
Are you all copies, too?
It's likely that the nature of
"Nyamazon," Mizuho's power, is copying.
But if that's the case...
Those cats can't bring living creatures.
It doesn't add up.
He was definitely close to
the truth about going adrift.
Mizuho, can I borrow your cat?
There's something I want to investigate.
Okay.
Oh, hey...!
Ow!
You are a cat. Your name is Tora.
Are you the one who coughed up a
hairball on my keyboard two days ago?
Good. Okay, next question.
This one has to do...
...with how you typically
bring us the things you do.
The things you bring back with you...
...are copies from the world
we're from, right?
If you answer me, I'll give you this.
Good boy. Next question.
You guys are lying to us, aren't you?
You really can bring back
living creatures, can't you?
You've been keeping that from us.
Because if people found out, it would
put Mizuho in a precarious spot.
So that's it, then. The reason we went
adrift is because Mizuho's power—
Wah! Hey, what are you doing?!
Ah, stop!
I was terrified that he
would announce it to everyone,
but instead, he went off on his
solo journey without saying a word.
He has a fine character,
for being so hairless.
Yes, it's not as though Mizuho
was the only cause of this.
Going adrift was nothing that could be
stopped.
He was well aware of that fact.
When we gave him those sea monkeys
as a going-away present,
he seemed to be quite delighted.
I wish I could go back home.
How is it possible...
...that things have changed so much
over a single strand of hair?
Not a very tasty-looking animal.
Then again,
is it even possible that two copies were
made of someone from our own world?
That kind of sounds like
someone screwed up their order, huh?
Could it be that two copies just
happened to be made by accident?
Once they bring Kaga back,
we'll have all of us together.
Once we are, I wonder if we could
get you to take us to another world.
No.
We aren't leaving here
until Ms. Aki returns.
But...
Don't go thinking that there's a place
for people like you anywhere you go.
Tell me, when you say a "place,"
are you talking about this child's room
that you recreated from your own home?
If you don't have a power,
you can't live on your own, can you?
Someone has to be there to help you.
You're right. I may have been able
to survive in this world thanks to you.
Then do as I tell you to.
Then again, even so,
I'll thank you to let me
pick my place for myself.
You can't do anything by yourself, though.
Admit it already.
You're excess
baggage for everyone else.
Just because you have your lofty opinions
doesn't mean you can change anything.
Nozomi!
Leave her to herself.
She's just going to keep
slowing everyone else down.
Do you really mean that?
It would be...
...better if she didn't go with you.
That's not something that
you get to decide, Asakaze.
It's something for Nozomi to decide.
Stay away from me.
I'm not very good company right now.
I'm wondering if someone would
put an end to all of this for me.
The truth is, those kinds of slippery
thoughts are all I've been thinking.
I recognize this bear. It's the kind
they give you to celebrate a birth.
I had one at my place, too,
but I threw it out.
Why do you suppose that was?
Because the cats came to live with me.
Cats are nice and warm,
but bears are cold.
'Cause they're dead.
You can talk to them,
but they never respond,
and the consistency of their fur is
different.
You know, 'cause they're dead.
Yeah, well, I...
threw mine away, too.
When night comes, she can't
even go up the stairs by herself.
I'll bet that right now,
she's trembling in fear from the storm.
We can't live with her
in that house anymore.
I know that we're going
to end up getting split up.
She's just a child.
She's still just a little—
I've always wondered...
...what is the point of this?
What can you do with that toy?
Just how far have you fallen?
Ever since that day, when another me
started walking around on his own,
it has been my only wish
to do away with you.
That's more than you can handle.
You and I both have the same power.
You do actually understand, don't you?
That Seiji can't win?
That's why you pray.
Yeah, that's right.
Catch!
Today, we fight with these!
That's it.
Always reaching the
same outcome must be dull, right?
These are special guns.
This is what's called a "Skip."
At last, my wish has come true.
Sakura!
Stop! That's my sacrifice to God!
This cat is still alive!
Nothing ever changes if you
keep clinging to somebody!
You just have to deal
with things yourself!
It's too cold out here.
I did manage to change, thanks to you.
Because you showed me the light.
Let's go back.
Mm-hmm.
Congratulations.
You win.
How does it feel,
now that you're the victor?
Yeah, somehow...
...it feels awfully hollow.
Why is that?
Because now, I don't know...
...what I should do.
Ah, they're back.
It's the medicine I ordered for Sakura.
Hmm? Say, what is she
always doing, anyway?
Sakura is a born lazybones.
Hmm, she seems like the smartest one, too.
I have to get going.
Huh? What fun is it to go
together with those guys?
Well, you may be right, but still...
I have to go.
Nozomi, I'll be in touch.
Mm-hmm.
Bye-bye.
All that remains is a gaping hole, huh?